//array of objects.  each element is an object containing a question, an array of choices, correct choice (which element of choices array)
var allQuestions = [

	{
			question : "When was Captain America born?",
			choices : ["During WW1","During WW2","During WW3","1994","2011"],	
			correctChoice : 1
	},
	{
			question : "What is Peter Parker's Middle name?",
			choices : ["Benjamin","William","John","Spidey","Steve"],	
			correctChoice : 0
	},
	{
			question : "Which Villan is looking/possed all of the Inifity Stones?",
			choices : ["Winter Soldier","Ultron","Loki","Thanos","Galactus"],	
			correctChoice : 3
	},
	{
			question : "What is the Black Widow's Real name?",
			choices : ["Natalie Porter","Romanov","Natalia Romanova","Natasha White","None of the above"],	
			correctChoice : 2
	},
	{
			question : "What is Hawkeye's Real name?",
			choices : ["Clint Eastwood","Clint Barton","Jeremy Rener","Chris Cox","Harold Johnson"],	
			correctChoice : 1
	},
	{
			question : "Name Peter Parker's Parents",
			choices : ["No one","Frank and Alice Parker","Richard and Mary Parker","Benjamin and May Parker","Tony and Pepper Stark"],	
			correctChoice : 2
	},
	{
			question : "Who is regarded as the inventor of the Marvel universe?",
			choices : ["Stan Lee","Nick Fury","Patrick Wu","Christopher Reeve","Angelo Bovino, Franklin Dawes"],	
			correctChoice : 0
	},
	
	{
			question : "Which member of the Guardians of the Galaxy is related to Thanos?",
			choices : ["Gamora","Drax the Destroyer","Groot","Star-Lord","Rocket-Racoon"],	
			correctChoice : 0
	},
	{
			question : "In Civil War, Iron Man fought against which Avenger?",
			choices : ["Superman","Captain America","Batman","Vision","Brainiac-7"],	
			correctChoice : 1
	},
	{
			question : "Who is Ant-Man?",
			choices : ["Anthony Ant","Clint Barton","Slade Wilson","Wade Wilson","Henry Pym"],	
			correctChoice : 4
	},
	{	
			question : "Which of the following characters can be seen in The Avengers?",
			choices : ["Nick Fury","Beast","Iron Fist","Captain Marvel","Green Lantern"],
			correctChoice : 0
	},
	{		question : "What/who was Daredevil blinded by?",
			choices : ["Bullseye","Toxic Waste","Jack 'The Devil' Murdock","The Sun","The Moon"],
			correctChoice : 1
	},
	{
			question : "Who has never been a Spider-Man movie villain?",
			choices : ["Green Goblin","Venom","Sandman","Doc Ock","Beetle"],
			correctChoice : 4
	},
	{		
			question : "What is the name of Iron Man's fellow captive in Afghanistan in the first Iron Man flick?",
			choices : ["Raza","Abu Bakaar","Obadiah","Howard Stark","Yinsen"],
			correctChoice : 4
	},
	{
			question : "Captain America's real name is:",
			choices : ["Chester Phillips","Steve Rogers","Timothy Dugan","James Buchanan Barnes","Roger Stevenson"],
			correctChoice : 1
	}
		

];